Marcel Breuer Papers
Marcel Breuer Papers
- Project Records, 1922-1982 (inclusive); 1940-1980 (bulk); 89 linear feet of manuscript material, 24,618 drawings, 6,160 photographs and slides.
  - THOMPSON HOUSE, Ligonier, PA (1947-1949) [Residential, Single]
    - Photographs, 118
      - Garage and Servants Quarters: South West Elevation [Roll 2, Frame 31], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View up Catilevered Stairs to Roof Terrace [Roll 2, Frame 30], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Roof Terrace [Roll 2, Frame 29], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Roof Terrace [Roll 2, Frame 28], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Roof Terrace [Roll 2, Frame 27], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North East Elevation with View of Roof Terrace [Roll 2, Frame 26], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Covered Passage to Service Entrance [Roll 2, Frame 25], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Garage and Servants Quarters: View Along South West Elevation [Roll 2, Frame 24], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation [Roll 2, Frame 23], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation Showing Entrance [Roll 2, Frame 22], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Entrance [Roll 2, Frame 21], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Entrance [Roll 2, Frame 20], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Entry Walk and Wall at Entrance [Roll 2, Frame 19], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation Showing Bedroom Windows [Roll 2, Frame 18], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation Showing Lattice in Stone Wall [Roll 2, Frame 17], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Approach to House [Roll 2, Frame 16], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Approach to House [Roll 2, Frame 15], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Approach to House [Roll 2, Frame 14], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View Along South East Elevation [Roll 2, Frame 13], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - South East Elevation [Roll 2, Frame 12], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - South East Elevation [Roll 2, Frame 11], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - South East Elevation [Roll 2, Frame 10], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of Garden Retaining Walls and Trellis [Roll 2, Frame 9], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of Garden Retaining Wall and Trellis [Roll 2, Frame 8], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of Garden Retaining Wall and Trellis [Roll 2, Frame 7], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of Garden Retaining Wall and Trellis [Roll 2, Frame 6], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Cantilevered Stair and Roof Terrace [Roll 2, Frame 5], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Cantilevered Stair and Roof Terrace [Roll 2, Frame 4], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View Along South East Elevation [Roll 2, Frame 3], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Entrance [Roll 2, Frame 2], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Lattice in Stone Wall [board mounted, 14.75 x 17.25 in.] [Roll 2, Frame 1], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Approach to House [Roll 13, Frame 15], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Approach to House [Roll 13, Frame 16], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation [Roll 13, Frame 17], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Entrance [Roll 13, Frame 18], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation Showing Bedroom Windows [Roll 13, Frame 19], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation with Lattice [Roll 13, Frame 20], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation Showing Entrance [Roll 13, Frame 21], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation Showing Entrance [Roll 13, Frame 22], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Covered Passage Elevation [Roll 13, Frame 23], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Covered Passage [Roll 13, Frame 24], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Entrance [Roll 13, Frame 25], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Entry Walk and Wall at Entrance [Roll 13, Frame 26], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation Showing Lattice in Stone Wall [Roll 13, Frame 27], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation Showing Lattice in Stone Wall [Roll 13, Frame 28], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Pond and Lattice in Stone Wall [Roll 13, Frame 29], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Pond and Lattice in Stone Wall [Roll 13, Frame 30], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Pond and Lattice in Stone Wall [Roll 13, Frame 31], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Master Bedroom Terrace [Roll 13, Frame 32], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View Along North west Elevation [Roll 13, Frame 33], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View Along North West Elevation [Roll 13, Frame 34], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Approach to House [Roll 13, Frame 35], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - North West Elevation [Roll 13, Frame 36], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Covered Passage Elevation [Roll 13, Frame 37], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of Trellis with Cantilevered Stair [Slide 22], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - View from Living Room [Slide 328], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Cantilevered Stair and Roof Terrace [Slide 34], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Outside Stair Leading to Roof Deck [Slide 62], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - View of Entrance [Slide 65], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Part of East Elevation [Slide 68], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Plan [Slide 85], drawings, plan; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Wall at Entrance towards Servants Quarters [Slide 167], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Part of East Elevation [Slide 175], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Master Bedroom Terrace [Slide 177], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Approach to House [Slide 178], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - West Elevation [Slide 183], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - East Elevation [Slide 278], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Pond and Lattice in Stone Wall [Slide 644], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Cantilevered Stair and Roof Terrace [Slide 645], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Rear Entrance with Trellis [Slide 646], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Pond and Lattice in Stone Wall [Slide 765], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Exterior View of Terraced Landscaping with House Beyond [Slide 40], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Exterior View of Terraced Landscaping with House Beyond [Slide 643], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
  - THOST HOUSE, Hamburg, Germany (1926) [Interior]
    - Published Material
      - Studio, (Catalog) (Oversize 19, Folder 19)
      - Dining room and Music room, (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 19, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, 4
      - Living room with furniture ("wohn raum")., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 30)
      - Kids room with furniture ("kinderzimmer bei Thost") [photo by Consemuller Klischee], finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 30)
      - Nursery furniture., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 30)
      - Wooden Drawer Units. [Slide 673], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
  - TIBBY HOUSE, Port Washington, NY (1952-1953) (not built) [Residential, Single]
    - Drawings, 14
      - Annotated Blueline Preliminary Drawings, [Design Development Drawings]; 3; (reproductions) (Tube 648)
      - Prelim. Presentation Sheet with Multiple Drawings; Prelim. Plans, [Design Development Drawings]; 3; (originals) (Tube 648)
      - Exterior Rendered Perspective from Above, [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 648)
      - Plot Plans, Floor Plans, Section, Elevations, Details, [Working Drawings]; 6; (originals) (Tube 648)
      - Framing Plans and Details, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 648)
    - Project Files
      - Bid Documents (Feb 1953-Mar 1953) (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Client (Sep 1952-Apr 1953), John and Emily Tibby (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Financial Records (Jan 1953-Apr 1953), Architectural Invoices (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Program Documents, Manuscript ("Notes About Our House"), sketches and program description (composed by client) (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Specifications (13 Feb 1953), General Specifications (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Transmittals (Nov 1952-Feb 1953) (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - TILLEY HOUSE, Red Bank, NJ (1949-1950) [Residential, Single]
    - Drawings, 1
      - Tilley House Revisions: Fireplace, Staircase, East Elevation, Bedroom No. 1, etc. (Dwg. No. 12), [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 602)
    - Project Files
      - Correspondence: Client (Aug 1949-Sep 1950), Alvin R. Tilley (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (Sep 1949-Jun 1950), Murphy-Brinkworth Construction Corp. (Gen. Contractor) (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Misc. Contractors and Manufacturers (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Financial Records I (Oct 1949-Jul 1950), Architectural Invoices (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Financial Records II, Certificates of Payment (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Office Records, Miscellaneous Notes and Sketches (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Specifications, Description of Basic Three-Bedroom House Model, Addendum, Lighting Fixture Schedule (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - TOMPKINS HOUSE, Hewlett Harbor, NY (1945-1946) [Residential, Single]
    - Drawings, 21
      - Magazine Clippings on Board- Plans and Perspective, [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Schematic Plans and Elevations, [Design Development Drawings]; 3; (s) (Tube 642)
      - Sketches/Drafts, [Design Development Drawings]; 2; (s) (Tube 642)
      - Plans, Sections, Elevations, Details, [Working Drawings]; 7; (originals) (Tube 642)
      - Framing Plan and Section, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 642)
      - Heating Plan, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 642)
      - Electrical- Plan, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 642)
      - Site/Landscaping- Plot Plan, Planting Plan, [Working Drawings]; 2; (originals) (Tube 642)
      - Seawane Estates (Hewlett Harbor, Long Island) Plan, [Site Surveys]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 642)
      - Heating Plan (office copy)., [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 642)
      - Electrical Plan (office copy)., [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 642)
    - Project Files
      - Correspondence: Client: Gilbert Tompkins (1945-48) (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Contractor: Gordon Roth (1945-47) (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers/Suppliers (1945-49) (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Publicity (1947-48), Architectural Forum, List of International Publications (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Financial Records, Invoices for Architectural Services (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Promotional Materials: Hewlett Harbor (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Specifications/ Schedules, General Specifications, Heating Specifications (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - List of Drawings [8 Nov 1945] (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Published Material
      - The Tompkins House Architectural Record (Sept 1947), 67-73; (tear sheet) (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, 24
      - View from southeast., finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 2 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - South façade., finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 2 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - West façade., finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - View from southwest., finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Living room with fireplace., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 2 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - View of living room through fireplace., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Stairs., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 2 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Kitchen., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Dining room., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Bed room., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Model, (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - View of Two Elevations at Corner [dup SL-761] [Slide 798], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View Along South Façade [Slide 799], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - South Elevation [Slide 800], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Elevation with Terrace Railing [Slide 801], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Service Yard [Slide 613], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - View through Living Room Fireplace [Slide 713], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - [Slide 33], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Elevation [Slide 315], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - Suspended Staircase [Slide 594], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
      - View of Two Elevations at Corner [Slide 761], finished project, exterior view; (color slides) 1 (Box SL-8)
  - TORIN CORPORATION (NIVELLES), Nivelles, Belgium (1963-1964) [Commercial], (Alternate names: Torrington Manufacturing Co. (Nivelles, Belgium)/TSA Division)
    - Drawings, 87
      - Revision of South Road and Parking [Oct-Nov 1969] (2 sheets), [Working Drawings]; 2; (originals) (Tube 266)
      - Site Plan [12 Sep 1969] (2 copies), [Presentation Drawings]; 2; (reproductions) (Tube 266)
      - Design Development Sketches and Drawings [Dec 1962-Sep 1964] (includes rough sketches by MB): including precast panel and façade studies, window details, preliminary site plans, office layout plans, schemetic plans, preliminary schemes, structural details, plan studies and office elevations, [Design Development Drawings]; 62; (mixed) (Tube 266)
      - Proposed Changes and Torrington S.A. [22 Sep 1967], [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 266)
      - Office Lighting (Dwg. No. SK3) [7 Mar 1963], [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 267)
      - Drip Details (Dwg. No. SK1A) [15 Jul 1969], [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 267)
      - Office Partitions (Dwg. No. F1-F2) [20 Apr 1964], [Working Drawings]; 2; (originals) (Tube 267)
      - Construction Set [Feb-Apr 1963]: Dwg. Nos. A1-A8, [Working Drawings]; 8; (originals) (Tube 267)
      - Exterior Elevations (Dwg. No. A3A) [9 Jul 1969], [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 267)
      - Hanger to Fasten Crane to Concrete Beams ("office file") [n.d.], [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 267)
      - Factory Sign [5 Jun 1964] (Chermayeff and Geismar), [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 267)
      - Office Lighting and Electrical (Dwg. No. SK1-SK2) [8 Mar 1963], [Working Drawings]; 2; (reproductions) (Tube 267)
      - Construction Set [Feb-Apr 1963] (annotated prints): Dwg. Nos. A1, A2, A7, [Working Drawings]; 3; (reproductions) (Tube 267)
    - Project Files
      - Correspondence (1963-1968), Branch Manager: Kenneth Crowe (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Published Material
    - Photographs, 49
      - Concrete precast wall panels, construction, detail; (color photographs) 5 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Construction progress with annotations on reverse (8 Nov. 1963), construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 8 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Construction progress with annotations on reverse (6 Dec. 1963), construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 6 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Construction progress with annotations on reverse (10 Jan. 1964), construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 4 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Construction progress with annotations on reverse (15 Feb. 1964), construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 6 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Construction progress with annotations on reverse (30 May 1964), construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 6 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Single concrete wall panel frame and finished panel, construction, detail; (black and white photographs) 6 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Details of east façade made of precast panels, construction, detail; (black and white photographs) 8 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - TORIN CORPORATION (OAKVILLE), Oakville, Ontario, Canada (1952-1953) [Commercial], (Alternate names: Ontario (Oakville) Plant/Torrington Manufacturing Co./Canadian Division)
    - Drawings, 19
      - Plan of Part of Lot 17, Con. 3, S.D.S. [11 May 1953], [Site Surveys]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 1147)
      - Presentation Set (3 schemes): Elevations, Floor Plan and Site Plan, [Presentation Drawings]; 3; (originals) (Tube 1147)
      - Presentation Set (2 schemes): Elevations, Floor Plan and Site Plan, [Presentation Drawings]; 2; (originals) (Tube 1147)
      - Presentation Set (2 schemes): Elevations, Floor Plan and Site Plan [annotated prints], [Presentation Drawings]; 2; (reproductions) (Tube 1147)
      - Perspective of Façade and Main Entrance [graphite on trace], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1147)
      - Manufacturing Unit: Typical Plan Layout [11 May 1953], [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1147)
      - Wall Section, [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1147)
      - Manufacturing Unit: Details of Brick Pier Cement Cap [12 Oct 1953], [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1147)
      - Manufacturing Unit: Typical Layout. Construction Set [Jun-Oct 1953]: Drawings 1-7 of numbered set: Plans, Wall Sections, Elevations, Details, [Working Drawings]; 7; (originals) (Tube 1147)
    - Project Files
    - Published Material
      - Factory by Marcel Breuer is Bright Architectural Forum (Feb 1955), 7 pgs.; (Reprint) (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - Photographs, 7
      - Front elevation and entrance, finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 3 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Façade, finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Rear elevation, finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Entrance façade, finished project, detail; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Sunshade detail [negative image], finished project, detail; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - TORIN CORPORATION (PENRITH), Penrith, Australia (1976) [Commercial], (Alternate names: Torrington Manufacturing Company (Penrith, Australia))
    - Drawings, 53
      - Preliminary [23 Apr 1974]: Dwg. Nos. 1-5 and 1A), [Design Development Drawings]; 6; (originals) (Tube 1399)
      - Design Development Drawings [Jan 1974-Dec 1974]: including façade studies, elevations studies, proposed site plan, stair sections and preliminary schemes, [Design Development Drawings]; 27; (originals) (Tube 1399)
      - Topographic Maps: Town of Penrith (with trace paper overlay), [Site Surveys]; 2; (reproductions) (Tube 1400)
      - Scheme 3A [28 Dec 1973] (annotated prints), [Design Development Drawings]; 4; (reproductions) (Tube 1400)
      - Presentation Sheet: Floor Plan [n.d.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 1400)
      - Torrington, U.K.D. Construction Set (date stamped 10 Oct 1973 on verso) (annotated prints, probably used as reference drawings): Architectural (A2-A8, and photostat copy), [Working Drawings]; 8; (reproductions) (Tube 1400)
      - Preliminary [14 Jun 1974] ("office copy"): Dwg. Nos. 1-5, [Design Development Drawings]; 5; (reproductions) (Tube 1400)
    - Photographs, 20
      - Construction progress, construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 20 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - TORIN CORPORATION (ROCHESTER, IND.), Rochester, IN (1960-1968) [Commercial], (Alternate names: Torrington Manufacturing Co. (Rochester, Ind.))
    - Drawings, 85
      - Mezzanine Renovation (Dwg. No. 1) [26 Jul 1978], [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1396)
      - Addition. Construction Set [9 Feb 1962]: Architectural (A1-A3), [Working Drawings]; 3; (originals) (Tube 1396)
      - Construction Set [1 Feb 1960]: Architectural (A1-A10), Structural (S1-S5), Plumbing (P1-P3), Site Plumbing (SP1), Electrical (E1-E4), HVAC (HVAC1-HVAC2), [Working Drawings]; 25; (originals) (Tube 1396)
      - SK Drawings [Sep-Nov 1959]: Dwg. Nos. SK1-SK13, incomplete, [Design Development Drawings]; 8; (originals) (Tube 1397)
      - Office Furnishing Layout [5 Feb 1963], [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1397)
      - Misc. SK Drawings and unnumbered sheets [Feb 1960-Feb 1961], [Design Development Drawings]; 4; (originals) (Tube 1397)
      - Office Extension [13 Jan 1965], [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1397)
      - Construction Set [1 Feb 1960] (annotated prints): Plumbing (P1-P3), Site Plumbing (SP1), Electrical (E1-E4), HVAC (HVAC1-HVAC2), [Working Drawings]; 10; (reproductions) (Tube 1397)
      - Construction Set [1 Feb 1960] ("contract issue"): Architectural (A1-A10), Structural (S1-S5), Plumbing (P1-P3), Site Plumbing (SP1), HVAC (HVAC1-HVAC2), Electrical (E1-E4), [Working Drawings]; 24; (reproductions) (Tube 1398)